Inventory of the Charles Campbell Papers 1743-1896
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Family and Professional Papers (Box 2-17)
  - Letters, 1840-1849., 505 items. (Box 4-7)
    - Letters, 1847., 61 items. (Box-folder 6:40-100)
      - A. B. Guijon, Washington to [Charles] Campbell, Petersburg, 22 February 1847., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:49)
        Letter concerns Force's Historical Tracts. Discussion of Bacon's Rebellion. Is sending "An Account of Bacon's Rebellion in the Year 1776"[sic]. Has decided to enter college.
      - [Elizabeth Campbell Maben], Richmond to Mrs. Mildred W. Campbell, Petersburg, 26 February 1847., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 6:50)
        $3000 collected for "the Irish." Social news.
        Postscript: Campbell Maben to [Callaway Campbell]. His mother (Elizabeth Maben) has been reading Charles Campbell's History of Virginia. 1 page.
        Postscript: Jennie Maben to [Mildred W. Campbell]. Hopes she is successful with her school. 1 page.
      - E. Lorraine, Richmond, [Virginia] to Cha[rle]s Campbell, 28 February 1847., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:51)
        Thanks him for $15; asks him to recommend the family boarding house to others.
      - Ar[thur] H[azelrigg] Henley, Chota, [Tennessee] to Charles [Campbell], 1 March 1847., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 6:52)
        Sends $85 for his ward; has been sick; family news.
      - Charles Campbell, Petersburg to Alex[ande]r Guijon, Washington, 1 March 1847., 1 page. ACyS. (Box-folder 6:53)
        Asks him to bring a copy of Peter Forces' Historical Tracts with him to Richmond.
      - K. B. Townley, Lynchburg, Virginia to "friend" [Charles Campbell], 2 March 1847., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 6:54)
        Wants to know what ship Richard Townley arrived in during the 17th century.
      - A. B. Guiion, Washington to [Charles] Campbell, 4 March 1847., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:55)
        Discussion of the Senate meeting. Debts of the Senators. Social life in Washington.
      - [Charles Campbell], Petersburg, [Virginia] to [K. B.] Townley, Lynchburg, [Virginia], 6 March 1847., 2 pages. ACy. (Box-folder 6:56)
        Does not know the name of the vessel Richard Townley arrived in; suggests ways of finding the information.
      - W[illiam] Henry Foote, Romney to [Benjamin B.] Minor,12 March 1847., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:57)
        Has read Campbell's History as published in Southern Literary Messenger. Inquires as to whether 1619 or 1620 is the correct date for the introduction of slaves in Virginia. Asks Campbell to settle the matter, over which there has been some dispute.
      - [Charles Campbell], Petersburg to B[enjamin] B. Minor,[Richmond], 24 March 1847., 2 pages. AL. (Box-folder 6:58)
        Explains his view of certain financial aspects of the publication of his History. Will attend the next meeting of the historical society if he can, but will be unable to write anything for it.
      - Sam[ue]l D. Campbell, Natural Bridge, Virginia to Charles Campbell, Petersburg, Virginia, 25 March 1847., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:59)
        Gilmore family history; Campbell family history; Revolutionary war; glad Virginia Historical Society was revived.
      - Charles Campbell, Petersburg to Benj[amin] B. Minor,30 March 1847., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 6:60)
        Has read, corrected, and returned proof sheet. Sends references and a note on an aspect of the History for inclusion.
        Draft duplicate of this letter listed below.
      - Charles Campbell, Petersburg to [Benjamin B. Minor, Richmond]. ALS. 1 page. 30 March 1847. (Box-folder 6:61)
        Draft duplicate of letter of 30 March 1847.
        See above for the final copy of this letter with the same date.
      - E. Lorraine, Richmond, [Virginia] to Charles Campbell, Petersburg, Virginia, 31 March 1847., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 6:62)
        Returns the $15 he borrowed; is working as a bookkeeper; expects to work for James River and Kanawha County.
      - [Charles Campbell], Petersburg to W[illia]m H. Foote, Rowney, Virginia, 5 April 1847., 2 pages. AL. (Box-folder 6:63)
        Thanks him for favorable comments on the History of Virginia. Discusses date of introduction of slaves into Virginia.
      - [Charles Campbell] to [?], Timber Neck, Gloucester County,[Virginia], 15 May 1847., 2 pages. ACy. (Box-folder 6:64)
        Asks him to return the copy of Stith to Mr. Robins; will publish his own history soon; hopes to get a copy of Smith.
      - Charles Campbell, Petersburg, [Virginia] to Patrick Henry Aylett, Montville, King W[illia]m County,6 June 1847., 3 pages. ACyS. (Box-folder 6:65)
        Thinks everyone should be involved in the Presidential campaign; is satisfied with the nominees, Cass and Butler, and expects them to win.
      - A[lexander] S. C[ampbell], Warrenton to Charles Campbell, Petersburg, 29 June 1847., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:66)
        Thanks him for books sent him. Has been reading about farming and is becoming more enthusiastic about it. Looking forward to visit from Mother and Callaway. Has not yet read his History of Virginia.
      - John N. Rose, Memphis, Tennessee to Charles C. Campbell, Petersburg, Virginia, 30 June 1847., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 6:67)
        Character reference for Michael D. Deadrick.
      - Elliot M. Braxton, Mantua to Charles Campbell, Petersburg, 1 July 1847., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:68)
        Is visiting his father; is a lawyer.
      - Charles Campbell, Petersburg to Elliot M. Braxton, King and Queen, 12 July 1847., 3 pages. ACyS. (Box-folder 6:69)
        Patrick Henry anecdote; would like to visit; will send a copy of his book to cousin Sally; "Petersburg is of all places the hottest and dullest"; asks for tombstone epitaphs.
      - M[ildred] W. Campbell, Richmond to Charles [Campbell], 3 August 1847., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:70)
        Acknowledges receipt of $200. Local news: choosing of a new Presbyterian pastor.
      - B[enjamin] Silliman, New Haven, Connecticut to Rev. Stephen Taylor, 10 August 1847., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:71)
        Acknowledges receipt of the truffles he sent.
      - M[ildred] W. Campbell, Warrenton to Charles [Campbell], 16 August 1847., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:72)
        Her journey to Warrenton to Calloway. Family news.
      - Elizabeth M. M[aben], White Sulphur to Charles Campbell, Petersburg, 19 August [1847]., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:73)
        Arrived last Saturday, pleasantly located. Enjoying their stay at the resort. Zachary Taylor's son is there and Henry Clay left just before their arrival.
      - [Charles Campbell], Petersburg to Mrs. E[lizabeth] M. Maben,27 August 1847., 2 pages. AL. (Box-folder 6:74)
        Glad to hear news of her journey to the White Sulphur springs. News received from Mother about Callaway, Aleck, and his wife.
      - John Tyler, New York to Charles Campbell, 31 August 1847., 4 pages. LS. (Box-folder 6:75)
        Account of family, particularly of his father.
      - C[harle] C[ampbell], Petersburg to Mrs. Mildred W. Campbell. 3 September 1847., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:76)
        News of home. Reference to his writing a book.
        Letter also includes the letter of C[harles] C[ampbell], Petersburg, to Cally [Campbell]. Encourages him to practice writing. ALS. 2 pages.
      - [?], Norborne to Charles Campbell, Petersburg, [Virginia], 4 September 1847., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 6:77)
        Returns a book.
      - C[harles] Campbell, Petersburg, [Virginia] to Mr. Macfarlane, 6 September 1847., 1 page. ACyS. (Box-folder 6:78)
        Complains about paying too much postage on his proof sheets; the Messenger is for sale.
      - W[illiam] B. Harrison, Sweet Springs, Virginia to Charles Campbell, Petersburg, [Virginia], 14 September 1847., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:79)
        Thanks him for data on Harrison family; Harrison family data.
      - [Charles Campbell], Petersburg to B[enjamin] B. Minor,[Richmond], 15 September 1847., 2 pages. AL. (Box-folder 6:80)
        Sends more of manuscript of his History, leaving it to printer of Messenger to be divided up between now and the end of the year. Understands Minor is interested in selling the Messenger, but he prefers to remain in editing rather than publishing it.
      - J[ohn] M[oncure] Daniel, Richmond to [Charles] Campbell, 24 September 1847., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:81)
        "Little John" Thompson purchased Southern Literary Messenger yesterday from [Benjamin B.] Minor for about $2000. Financial situation of Messenger uncertain; Daniel had offered $1500 for it; Thompson knows nothing of this. Their friend [Charles Tyler] Botts is starting out for California.
      - [Charles Campbell], Petersburg to Mrs. M[ary] B. Carter, Shirley, 25 September 1847., 2 pages. AL. (Box-folder 6:82)
        Sorry to have missed her while she was in Petersburg. Speaks of his nervous condition and the necessity of his retirement to the country.
      - [Charles Campbell], Petersburg to John M. Daniel, Richmond, 27 September 1847., 2 pages. ACy. (Box-folder 6:83)
        The Messenger's subscription list is declining; doesn't think literary periodical would ever flourish in the South.
      - J[ohn] R. Thompson, Richmond to [Charles Campbell], 2 October 1847., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 6:84)
        Mr. Macfarlane has no copies of his History of Virginia and would like some. Greets Campbell, hopes he will continue to aid Southern Literary Messenger of which he, Thompson has just become editor.
      - John R. Thompson, Richmond to C[harles Campbell], [Petersburg], 6 October 1847., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:85)
        Asks him whether the conclusion of his History should be published in the December or the January issue of the Messenger. When he comes to Richmond, Thompson will show him some interesting autograph letters.
      - C[harles] Campbell, Petersburg to John R. Thompson, [Richmond], 8 October 1847., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:86)
        Informs Thompson of the agreement with Benjamin B. Minor to have the History of Virginia complete in the 1847 volume of the Messenger, even if this meant devoting the entire December issue to it.
      - Charles Campbell, Petersburg to Alex[ander] S. Campbell,26 October 1847., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:87)
        Will visit him early next week. Relates news of a fire in house and stable of John and Betty Maben: fires were deliberately set.
      - [Charles Campbell], Richmond to Mildred Ruffin, Marlbourn, Hanover, 29 October 1847., 1 page. ACy. (Box-folder 6:88)
        Will visit Marlbourn.
      - S. S. Braxton, Fredericksburg to Charles [Campbell], 5 November 1847., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:89)
        Thanks him for his gift.
      - Kate [Beckwith], Petersburg, [Virginia] to Anna Burdsall, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 8 November 1847., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:90)
        Hopes her brother will be well.
      - Arthur H[azelrigg] Henley, Chota, [Tennessee] to Charles Campbell, Petersburg, Virginia, 11 November 1847., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:91)
        Family news; will send $150 for his ward's expenses; sold a slave, Tom, so that he could be near his wife; slave, Rose, which belongs to Charles Campbell's son now, has 10 children and Arthur Hazelrigg Henley may let her try to run a farm on her own.
      - Scott [Burdsall] and J. M. N., Augusta to Anna Burdsall, Petersburg, Virginia, 23 November 1847., 3 pages. LS. (Box-folder 6:92)
        Took a steam boat to Charleston and will go to Montgomery. J. M. N. to Anna Burdsall. Invites her to visit.
      - A. E. Peticolas[?], Richmond, [Virginia] to Charles Campbell, 25 November 1847., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 6:93)
        Asks for a friend's manuscript.
      - E[lliott] M. Braxton, King and Queen C[our]t House to Charles Campbell, Petersburg, Virginia, 30 November 1847., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 6:94)
        His fiancee rejected him and he is depressed.
      - [Charles Campbell] to Alex[ander] S. Campbell, Warrenton, December 1847., 2 pages. Fragment. AL. (Box-folder 6:95)
        His trip from Warrenton to Richmond where he stayed with [Edmund] Ruffin for a week. Will have his History bound shortly and still uncertain if he will profit by it.
      - Henry T. Oates, Charleston to Cha[rle]s Campbell, 7 December 1847., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 6:96)
      - W[illia]m Maxwell, Richmond to Cha[rle]s Campbell, [Petersburg], 8 December 1847., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 6:97)
        Sends him a prospectus of his work, hoping Campbell will be able to obtain subscribers for it. Asks if he will attend the Annual Meeting of the Virginia Historical Society on December 16th.
      - Charles Campbell, Petersburg, [Virginia] to Henry T. Oates, 11 December 1847., 1 page. ACyS. (Box-folder 6:98)
      - C[harles] Campbell, Petersburg to R. R. Howison, Richmond, 11 December 1847., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 6:99)
        His History of Virginia is currently in press at the office of the Southern Literary Messenger. He will send him the proof sheet when they become available.
      - J[ohn] M. Daniel, Richmond to [Charles Campbell, Petersburg], [Late 1847]., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 6:100)
        Asks for unbound sheets of the History which has been appearing in the Messenger; he would like to bind them himself.
    - Letters, 1848., 70 items. (Box-folder 7:1-69)
      - Charles Campbell to Thomas H. Williamson, [1848]., 2 pages. ACy. (Box-folder 7:1)
        Comment on Cavaliers and Puritans article; does not know the Bacon coat of arms.
      - M[ary] B. C[arter],[Shirley] to [Mildred W. Campbell], [Petersburg], [1848]., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 7:2)
        Sends son Charley back to school today. Encloses $50; asks her to buy various articles of clothing.
      - Mary B. Carter, [Shirley] to Mildred W. Campbell, Petersburg, 1 January 1848., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 7:3)
        Sends a barrel of food. Will get several copies of Charles' new History shortly. Family news.
      - Lyman C. Draper, Baltimore to Charles Campbell, Petersburg, 13 January 1848., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 7:4)
        His 1846 journey to the West was very successful. Was in Richmond last July, but ill-health prevented him from going to Petersburg. Is working on a volume The Life and Times of George Rogers Clark. Congratulates him on appearance of History of Virginia.
      - William Maxwell, Richmond to Charles Campbell, 17 January 1848., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 7:5)
        Received Charles Campbell's letter with $6 enclosed, six subscriptions to William Maxwell's Historical Register. Lists names. Thanks for copies of Charles Campbell's History. Will try to help sell and circulate Charles Campbell's book.
      - John M. Mason, Washington to C[harles] C[ampbell], 21 January 1848., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 7:6)
        Letter concerns history of Bacon's Rebellion, printed in the Southern Literary Messenger; no means of franking book Charles Campbell wishes to send to Library of Congress or to Smithsonian.
      - J[ames] W. Alexander, New York to Charles Campbell, [Petersburg], 24 January 1848., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 7:7)
        Has received his letter, but his book has yet to arrive. Regret that he will not have time to review it.
      - Jared Sparks, Cambridge, Massachusetts to Charles Campbell, [Petersburg], 25 January 1848., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 7:8)
        Is glad to hear the History of Virginia has been published. Asks for a copy for himself and one for Francis Bowen, editor of the North American Review.
      - A[lexander] S. Campbell, Warrenton to Charles Campbell, Petersburg, February 1848., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 7:9)
        Encloses partial payment of debts. Announces birth of second son, named William Horner. Has seen advertisements for his History but has yet to see the book itself.
      - Charles Campbell, Petersburg to Jared Sparks, Cambridge, Massachusetts, [2] February 1848., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 7:10)
        Sends him two copies of the History of Virginia. Asks how he can send copies to George Bancroft in London. Tells him of the revival of the Virginia Historical Society and its intention to publish a quarterly.
      - [Charles Campbell], Petersburg to [Jared Sparks, Cambridge, Massachusetts], 2 February 1848., 1 page. Draft. AL. (Box-folder 7:11)
        Sends him two copies of the History of Virginia Says he would like to send some copies to George Bancroft in London but he does not know how to reach him.
      - [Charles Campbell], Petersburg to Rev. J. W. Alexander, New York, 7 February 1848., 2 pages. ADf. (Box-folder 7:12)
        Believes would be interested in information of the Davies family. Sent copy of Charles Campbell's book. Questions using extensive quotes in original obsolete form, vs. modernized shorter quotes. If book sells well, may put out "handsome" edition. Sends copy to Tribune, Horace Greeley, editor, for whom he wrote some time ago; also a copy to the Literary World.
      - A[lexander] S. Campbell, Warrenton to Charles [Campbell], 18 February 1848., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 7:13)
        Letter of introduction of Dr. Helms, who is investigating their claims upon government.
      - [Charles Campbell], [Petersburg] to [Alexander S. Campbell], [Warrenton], [March [?] 1848]., 2 pages. Fragment. AL. (Box-folder 7:14)
        Callaway may be going to Tennessee shortly. Met soldiers returning from Mexico. Family news.
      - Ar[thur] H[azelrigg] Henley, Madisonville to Charles Campbell, Petersburg, Virginia, 5 March 1848., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 7:15)
        Encloses $160 for his ward's expenses; 40 cases of measles on his plantation.
      - Lyman C. Draper, Baltimore to Charles Campbell, Petersburg, 6 March 1848., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 7:16)
        Has written a favorable review of the History of Virginia for the Literary World. He is writing only fitfully. Asks further information on Col. Alexander Spotswood Dandridge, mentioned in the History.
      - M[ary] B. Carter, Shirley to M[ildred] W. Campbell, Petersburg, 8 March 1848., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 7:17)
        She has read Charles's book and is delighted with it. Family news.
      - [Charles Campbell], Petersburg to [Lyman C. Draper, Baltimore], 8 March 1848., 2 pages. Draft. AL. (Box-folder 7:18)
        Thanks him for favorable reviews in Literary World, an extract of which his bookseller will use as advertisement. Suggests name of someone to write to for information on Col. Alexander Spotswood Dandridge.
      - [Charles Campbell], Petersburg to Lyman C. Draper, Philadelphia, 9 March 1848., 3 pages. Draft. AL. (Box-folder 7:19)
        Thanks him for favorable review in Literary World. He once had a letter of Col. A. S. Dandridge, which is now at Virginia Historical Society. He has received a letter from Jared Sparks, favorably commenting on the History.
      - [Charles Campbell, Petersburg] to Jared Sparks,[Cambridge, Massachusetts], 9 March 1848., 2 pages. Draft. AL. (Box-folder 7:20)
        Is glad to hear that Sparks approves of his History and hopes it will be noted in the North American Review.
      - R. C. Mason, near Alexandria to Charles Campbell, Petersburg, [Virginia], 10 March 1848., 8 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 7:21)
        Found error in History of Virginia. Jefferson not the author of the Bill of Rights, George Mason wrote it; cites evidence for this.
      - Marion R. Booth, Hawthorne Hall to Charles Campbell, Petersburg, Virginia, 15 March 1848., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 7:22)
        Will read his History of Virginia.
      - A[lexander] S. C[ampbell], Warrenton to Charles [Campbell], 16 March 1848., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 7:23)
        Has read favorable review of his History. More about Dr. Helms. Molley's health improving.
      - Jared Sparks, Cambridge, Massachusetts to Charles Campbell, Petersburg, Virginia, 21 March 1848., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 7:24)
        He does not object to the use of his comments on the History being made public. Discusses a factual question raised by Lyman C. Draper, and compares some historians to sheep. Says a note of the book will be made in a future issue of the North American Review.
      - [Charles Campbell], Petersburg to J. K. Tefft, Savannah, 24 March 1848., 1 page. AL. (Box-folder 7:25)
        Read with interest the proceedings of the Georgia Historical Society. Will send the Society a copy of his History of Virginia at the first opportunity. Says most Virginians are currently too "engrossed in president making" to notice his book.
      - R. K. Meade, Wash[ington] to C[harles] Campbell, 26 March 1848., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 7:26)
        Has met with the Secretary of the Treasury and Charles Campbell has been appointed a clerk.
      - R. C. Mason, near Alexandria to [Charles Campbell], 29 March 1848., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 7:27)
        Thanks Charles Campbell for attention to George Mason case.
      - [Charles Campbell], Petersburg to [John R. Thompson, Richmond], 11 April 1848., 2 pages. AL. (Box-folder 7:28)
        Sends correction of an item in last issue of Messenger. Encourages him to continue publishing even though these are bad times for "belles lettres".
      - J. K. Tefft, Savannah to Cha[rle]s Campbell,[Petersburg], 15 April 1848., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 7:29)
        Has just returned from Europe. Suggests ways of sending the History of Virginia to the Georgia Historical Society.
      - John F. Randolph, Yazoo City, Mississippi to Cha[rle]s Campbell, Petersburg, Virginia, 16 April 1848., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 7:30)
        Read Charles Campbell's works; recounts his life story.
      - Henry Barnard, Charleston, South Carolina to Charles Campbell, 18 April 1848., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 7:31)
        He is traveling with Mrs. Barnard, and they expect to spend time in the Norfolk-York-Richmond area. Hopes to meet Campbell and to introduce his wife to him.
      - [Charles Campbell], Petersburg to Henry Barnard, 20 April 1848., 3 pages. AL. (Box-folder 7:32)
        Is glad to hear that he and Mrs. Barnard will visit Virginia. Suggests places for them to visit. Hopes to join them.
      - Sam[ue]l D. Campbell, Natural Bridge, Virginia to [Charles Campbell], 29 April 1848., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 7:33)
        Thanks him for copies of his History of Virginia.
      - M. K. McGhee, Toquaville to Charles Campbell, Petersburg, Virginia, May [1848] [?]., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 7:34)
        Family news; remembers happy days at Chota.
      - Charles Campbell, Petersburg to Jared Sparks, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 2 May 1848., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 7:35)
        Sends him the requested copy of Kercheval's History. Encloses a list of more of the Bland manuscripts.
      - F[rancis] Wayland and R. A. Guild, Providence, Rhode Island to Charles Campbell, 3 May 1848., 1 page. LS. (Box-folder 7:36)
        Acknowledges gift of History of Virginia to Brown University Library.
      - N. Gammell[?], [Providence, Rhode Island] to Charles Campbell, 4 May 1848., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 7:37)
        Thanks him for the gift of his History to Brown University Library.
      - Henry Barnard. [Murfreesboro] to C[harles] Campbell, [Petersburg], 5 May 1848., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 7:38)
        He and his wife arrived this morning and would be happy to see him, even though he [Barnard] is ill.
      - [Charles Campbell], Petersburg to [Dr. Helm, Warrenton, Virginia (penciled in)], 17 May 1848., 2 pages. ADf. (Box-folder 7:39)
        Giving reference for quote from the Bland Papers on Colonel James Monroe.
      - M[ary] B. Carter, Shirley to [Mildred W.] Campbell, Petersburg, 10 June 1848., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 7:40)
        Family news: her children have joined the church, which is a great comfort to her. Her son, Will, is at Whig convention in Philadelphia.